Hadi Lashkari-Ghouchani

Senior Android Developer

@ hadilashkari@gmail.com

+98 939 125 8116

Tehran Iran

github.com/hadilq

stackoverflow.com/users/2482947 in linkedin.com/in/hadilq

SUMMARY

Professional guy with 3+ years of experience in Android development who has profound learning and contributing skills. Creative person who prefers to not reinventing the wheel, instead create a vehicle, but in case of performance, memory management, app size and security will invent a spherical wheel. A value oriented and passionate developer who enjoys solving problems and creating scalable, maintainable and efficient app to make the world better place to live.

EXPERIENCE

Lead Android Developer

at Sheypoor

🛗 Jan. 2018 - Present

Tehran, Iran

Sheypoor is one of lead classifieds marketplaces in Iran with over 1.5+ M users per day, 13+ M overall users and 344+ M sessions.

Missions:

- Increase the number of users per day from 0.5+ M to 1.5+ M in a year.
- As the functional manager of Android team, I'm responsible for the code quality of Sheypoor app. I coach the team to practice design patterns, clean code and using app architecture, along with updating libraries and adding new features with focus on agility and UX.
- · Implement new design of the entire app, including rebranding, for summer campaign.

Technologies:

- Dagger 2, RxJava 2, Butter Knife, Greendao, etc.
- · Agile, Kanban, Git Flow, CI/CD
- · Mockito, Espresso, Jacoco
- · Pivotal Tracker, Github, Jenkins, Slack, Zeplin, etc.

Senior Android Developer

at Myket

m Sep. 2015 - Des. 2017

Tehran, Iran

Myket is one of lead app stores in Iran with over 8+ M users.

Missions:

- · Starting TDD and installing Jenking's pipeline to handle CI/CD.
- Implementing features such as handling deeplinks, search page, inbox page, etc.

Technologies:

- · Volley, One Signal, EventBus, OrmLite, etc.
- · Agile, Scrum, Git Flow
- · Mockito, Espresso
- Atlassian Jira, Atlassian Confluence, Gitlab, Jfrog, Jenkins

Java and C# developer

at Soha System

mar. 2015 - Aug. 2015

O Tehran, Iran

SOHA was formed to focus on solutions based on smart cards.

ARTICLE

ProAndroidDev post: Logging in Kotlin

ProAndroidDev post: Reactive MVVM architectural pattern

ProAndroidDev post: Loading entities from database and server API by using RxJava

ProAndroidDev post: LiveData with single events

EDUCATION

Sharif University Of Technology Pavame-Noor University of Mashad

M.Sc B.Sc

in Physics in Physics

Feb. 2010 Jul. 2007

TOOLS / SKILLS

Android library

Dagger 2/RxJava 2/Retrofit 2 Butter Knife/JetPack/...

Android test library

JUnit/Mockito/Espresso/Jacoco/...

Tool

Gradle/Mayen/Ant/Make/Git/Subversion/...

Command Line Tool

grep/sed/netstat/awk/docker/... adb/sdkmanager/avdmanager/...

Development Tool

Pivotal Tracker/Jira/Jenkins/...

Programing Language

Java/Kotlin/Scala/Python Groovy/Dart/Javascript/Rust/...

Operating System

Linux(Fedora/Ubuntu)

LANGUAGE

English: Advance Farsi: Native

The source of this resume in github Built at December 20, 2018